Guide to the New York University Archives Collection of New York University COVID-19 Webpages MC.353
New York University Archives
- Steinhardt Remote Instruction Toolkit, July 2020-July 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
- Step 1: Pick Up Your Kit, September 2020-September 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
- Step 2: Activate Your Kit, September 2020-September 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
- Step 3: Collect Your Saliva Sample, September 2020-September 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
- Step 4: Return Your Kit, September 2020-September 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
- Student Advising, July 2021-January 2022 (Box Electronic Records)
- Student Financial Support, July 2021-August 2022 (Box Electronic Records)
- Student Financial Support, November 2020-July 2022 (Box Electronic Records)
- Student Housing, July 2021-August 2022 (Box Electronic Records)
- Student Housing, July 2020-July 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
- Student Return to Campus Testing and Quarantining, August-October 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
- Study and Remote Learning Spaces, September 2020-July 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
- Studying Abroad Go Local, August 2020-September 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
- Support Our Students, March-December 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
- Symptoms of COVID-19, August 2020-August 2022 (Box Electronic Records)
- Tandon School of Engineering COVID-19 Communications and Resources, July 2020-October 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
  This page lists resources available to Tandon community members, including faculty, students, and staff, as well as communications shared by the Dean of Tandon relating to the COVID-19 epidemic and the University's responses.
- Tandon Your Way, August 2020-June 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
- Teaching Technologies Toolkit (Gallatin), February-July 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
- Technology Enhanced Education (School of Global Public Health), February-July 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
- The Art of Social Distancing, May 2020-March 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
  This page includes submissions from members of the NYU community relating to art projects they've undertaken during COVID-19.
- The Coronavirus Aid, Relief, and Economic Security (CARES) Act Fund Disclosure, September 2020-June 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
  This page includes information about funding received by New York University under the federal CARES Act
- Thinking in Pandemic Times, April 2020-February 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
- Travel Information, March 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
- Travel Information, March-August 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
- Travel Policy, July 2021-August 2022 (Box Electronic Records)
- Travel Policy, July 2020-July 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
- Updates from Undergraduate Admissions, September 2020-March 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
  This page includes information about undergraduate admissions in Fall 2020.
- Vaccination Information Video, September 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
  On Friday, July 30, Dr. Carlo Ciotoli, Associate Vice President, NYU Student Health - GNU; Executive Director, Student Health Center, and Dr. Aisha Langford, Assistant Professor, Department of Population Health, NYU Langone, shared the latest data and answered questions about COVID-19 vaccines and the Delta variant.
- Vaccination Information: Public Health Benefits, August 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
- Vaccine Appointments, April 2021-July 2022 (Box Electronic Records)
- Vaccine Protocols, April 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
- Vaccine Questions and Support, April 2021-August 2022 (Box Electronic Records)
- Vaccine Requirement, August 2021-September 2022 (Box Electronic Records)
- Vaccine Requirement, April-October 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
- Vaccine Requirement: Academic Considerations, August 2021-August 2022 (Box Electronic Records)
- Vaccine Requirement: International Student Considerations, August 2021-August 2022 (Box Electronic Records)
- Vaccines at Langone, April-November 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
- Vaccines Off Campus, April 2021-August 2022 (Box Electronic Records)
- Vaccines On Campus, April 2021-August 2022 (Box Electronic Records)
- Violet Go, September 2022-ongoing (Box Electronic Records)
- Virtual Teaching Community, September 2020-September 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
- Visitors and Vendors, September 2021-August 2022 (Box Electronic Records)
- Who Do You Wear Your Mask For?, November 2020-March 2021 (Box Electronic Records)
  This video includes members of the University community talking about the reasons behind wearing a masks.
- Workplace Guidelines, July 2021-August 2022 (Box Electronic Records)
- Your Health and Care During the COVID-19 Outbreak, March-August 2020 (Box Electronic Records)
- Zooming In: Remote Learning Gets Creative, March 2020-September 2021 (Box Electronic Records)